utubejobs.com 2018-08-30

# More YouTube Views

Get More 

Views Now!

We Deliver Real Human Quality High Audience Retention YouTube Views

100% Safe Traffic

What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you place an order or fill out a form.   
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:   
To personalize your experience 

your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs

To process transactions 

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.   
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.   
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be kept on file for more than 60 days.   

Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information   
We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. 

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. 

Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at Terms Of Service

Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. 

Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.   
This policy was last modified on 12/06/2012 

Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.   
http://www.more-views.co   
P.O.Box 5475   
Ocean City, MD 21843   
United States   
Contact Us
